Welcome all of you inside Inspect Trade YouTube channel.
In today's video, we are going to talk
about the share price of ICICI Lambd.
Its target can be seen completely in
this video
and today we can see here that the
share of ICICI Lamborgh has closed
around
₹1880 and
it has earned a profit of ₹34.80
to the intraday traders.  So around 34
points have closed in profit today.
If we talk
about its performance here, then you can see that the
share of ICICI Lambd was sold today at an
intraday high of around
₹1842.  The intraday high there went up
to around ₹1883.  If we talk about the
movement here within 1 year, then within 1 year
we can see that the share of ICICI LBRD had gone down to
₹1480 and went up to around
₹2301.  Overall, if we talk about
volume, then here we can see that
around 734000 shares can be
seen being traded in the stock market, the
value of which you can see is
₹138 crores.  Overall, if we talk
here, as per the growth estimate, we
can see that 64% of the public can be seen
buying the shares of ICIC Lambar
and if we
talk about the trade setup, then you can do short term trade
with the shares of ICIC Lambd,
where you will buy or take entry
at around ₹1855, you can set a limit order
for tomorrow and after that
you will make a stop loss once you
get the entry at around
₹1810 and if I talk about the target, then you
can set the target at around
₹1910 as the first target and our second
target will be up
to ₹1940.  So you can see that it is quite good here,
you can get trading positions
and the points are also quite interesting.
Almost you can say that here you are
getting 90 to 85 points
in one trade which is going to be short term.  If you have
any doubt, you
can ask in the comment section below.  If you are new to the channel then
subscribe to this channel because I keep
publishing similar videos for you every day.  See you
in the next video.  Thank you for watching this
video guys.  Thank you.